<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Travel Photos App</string>
    <string name="travel_photos_app">Travel Photos App</string>
    <string name="taj_Mahal">The Taj Mahal is a mausoleum complex in Agra, India, that was built between 1631 and 1648. It is considered one of the world\'s most beautiful buildings and is visited by millions of tourists each year. The Taj Mahal was commissioned by the Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan as a tomb for his wife, Mumtaz Mahal. It is considered the finest example of Mughal architecture, which is a blend of Indian, Persian, and Islamic styles. The Taj Mahal is made of ivory-white marble and is located on the south bank of the Yamuna river.\nThe complex is believed to have been completed in 1653 at a cost of around ₹32 million, which in 2023 would be approximately ₹35 billion.</string>
    <string name="place2">sdgdfgss</string>
    <string name="place3">  wife, Mumtaz Mahal. It is considered the finest example of Mughal architecture, which is a blend of Indian, Persian, and Islamic styles. The Taj Mahal is made of ivory-wwife, Mumtaz Mahal. It is considered the finest example of Mughal architecture, which is a blend of Indian, Persian, and Islamic styles. The Taj Mahal is made of ivory-w</string>
    <string name="place4"> wife, made of ivory-w</string>
    <string name="place5"> wxample of Mughal architecture, which is a blend of Indian, Persian, and Islamic styles. The Taj Mahal is made of ivory-w</string>
    <string name="place6"> wife, Mumtaz Mahal. It is considered the finest example of Mughal architecture, which is a blend of Indian, Persian, and Islamic styles. The Taj Mahal is made of ivory-w</string>
    <string name="place7"> t is considered the finest example of Mughal architecture, which is a blend of Indian, Persian, and Islamic styles. The Taj Mahal is made of ivory-w</string>
    <string name="place8">mple of Mughal architecture, which is a blend of Indian, Persian, and Islamic styles. The Taj Mahal is made of ivory-w</string>
    <string name="place9"> wife, Mumtaz Mahal. It is considered the fine, which is a blend of Indian, Persian, and Islamic styles. The Taj Mahal is made of ivory-w</string>
    <string name="place10"> sidered the finest example of Mughal architecture, which is a blend of Indian, Persian, and Islamic styles. The Taj Mahal is made of ivory-w</string>
</resources>